

WEB DEVELOPER

Details

639099890243 rjimaw7777@gmail.com

Skills

HTML/CSS/JavaScript

MERN Stack

ServiceNow

Active Directory

Citrix

Hobbies

Reading, Netflix, Running

Links

LinkedIn

Languages

Filipino

English

Profile

Support Analyst for 3 years and counting dedicated to providing quality care for ultimate customer satisfaction . Proven ability to establish and maintain excellent communication and relationships with clients . Excellent time management skills combined with emotional intelligence . Patient and Hardworking . Doing web development as a hobby and planning to transition it to be my next working career

Employment History

Support Analyst First Line, ATOS, Eastwood Ave, Bagumbayan, Quezon City, 1110 Metro Manila, Philippines

NOVEMBER 2018 - 2021

- Created user accounts and managed access control.
- Supported users with software, hardware and network issues.
- Monitored help-desk and responded to incoming tickets to address support needs.
- Processed over 300+ support requests weekly for technical assistance on wide range of issues related to Account Unlocking and VPN Troubleshooting.
- Managed service follow-up communications, confirming satisfactory resolution of customers' service requests via email and phone.

Internships

Office Clerk, National Kidney and Transplant Institute, East Ave, Diliman, Quezon City

JUNE 2016 - NOVEMBER 2016

- Monitored premises, screened visitors, updated logs and issued passes to maintain security.
- Maintained organized files and stocked supplies to support team needs and maximize performance.
- Delivered clerical support by efficiently handling wide range of routine and special requirements.

Education

High School Diploma, Yverdon de Pestallozi School, Bulacan 2002 - 2012

Bachelor of Science and Information Technology, STI Fairview, Quezon City

Courses

Modern HTML & CSS From The Beginning (Including Sass), Udemy 2019

Modern JavaScript From The Beginning, Udemy

MERN eCommerce From Scratch, Udemy 2020

References

References available upon request

